Thank you for inviting me to the new version of Marvelous Designer's new function launch after last year.
First of all, I would like to introduce the content of the character's injury and how to make a reference.
And how to use multi-channel textures and Substance Painter for texturing.
And how to make costumes using Marvelous Designer.
And how to make a hair card using Ornatrix Hair.
Thank you.
Now I would like to introduce the content of the next version of Marvelous Designer's new function launch.
How to use multi-channel textures and Substance Painter for texturing.
And how to use multi-channel textures and Substance Painter for texturing.
I will introduce you to the workflow of creating a real-time character.
This is the final image of what I am going to introduce to you today.
It looks very natural, doesn't it?
Actually, I didn't model it. I just used the smartphone app, FaceApp, to make it fun.
What do you think about it?
Last time, I made a David Candy, and I applied FaceApp to it.
In the early 1980s,
I made a Japanese animation called Katchaman,
which was released under the name of the bookworm.
When I was young, I had a lot of fun watching it.
Among the five characters,
there is a character called Jun the Swan,
who represents a white swan.
I started thinking about what it would look like
if I made a real-time movie about this character.
In this animation,
there are five hero characters.
The third character is called Jun the Swan.
She is the symbol of the white swan,
and she is the only female character in the combination.
I've been thinking about
what it would look like
if I put this character in the movie.
So I started creating this.
As you can see,
I rode a motorcycle,
and I used a mobile phone like Yoyo,
and I wore a unique helmet,
a pink suit,
and a feather-shaped cape.
I wore a pink suit,
and I wore a feather-shaped cape.
and I wore a chemical-based hat,
Comfort armor,
I wore a defense armor.
I wore a mobile helmet,
and I wore a protective armor.
I wore a purple helmet.
I wore a yellow helmet
and a blue helmet.
I have been working on this character
since I was 16 years old.
I've been working on this character
I was making güçes like a monster.
It's like a monster.
If you wear normal clothes, you may be able to show the characteristics of SWAN better.
Even if many people can't tell that this is SWAN, it doesn't matter.
As long as you can bring some good memories to some people, that's enough.
The basic face and styling are decided by the early and middle-aged women in the 20s in Korea.
The style is similar to the style of the popular Korean vocalist.
I tried to make a lot of references that are similar to the feeling I think.
I didn't make a style that makes a certain character look like him.
I tried to make a face that is not in the world while thinking about the image of SWAN.
I think.
It is necessary to do facial modeling first.
The reference was created for 3D scan images.
I was curious about the shape of the face when I scanned the real person.
I modeled the face freely with ZBrush Dynamesh and Sculptris.
In the modeling process, I always pay attention not to deviate from the age of SWAN and the appearance I had designed.
I also thought about the size of the face.
I used ZBrush's G-LAP to get a well-organized topology.
As you can see, I wrapped the low-polygon mesh with the new high-polygon mesh.
As you can see, I wrapped the high-polygon mesh with the new high-polygon mesh.
I used ZBrush's Z-Wrap function to get the topology.
The left image is a dynamic wire.
The middle image is a wrapping of the existing low-poly bond.
The right image is a dynamic wire.
The left image is a dynamic wire.
The image represents the
I used 2 types of UV for the unravelling of the topology.
I used the UV area of the face as much as possible.
For better resolution, I divided the UV area into face and neck.
I used the UV area of the head and shoulders as much as possible.
I used the Re-Zone UV for the unravelling of the topology.
I used the UV area of the face as much as possible.
For better resolution, I divided the UV area into face and neck.
As you can see,
I used the multi-channel face of TEXTURING XYZ.
You can buy it on the website.
3 texture sources can be downloaded.
Albedo MAP.
This has the sliced SPHERALDE D-f Maurer skin.
There is a special availability for and in the utility MAP.
There is a special он storage for and in the utility MAP.
This is redder than the polystyrene.
It's a reddi-s birthday STEPHOGLOBIN MAP.
It's a redediOL frente TULIP.
After purchasing the material, you can download these three questionnaires.
In the albino map and the RGB channel, there is a displacement map and a utility map with different details.
And in the utility map, there is a hemoglobin map that shows all kinds of blood in the RGB channel,
and a melanin map and a specular map that shows all kinds of blood.
And in the z-wrap map, there is a plan that uses the same plan as the physical material,
and it is not blocked on the envelope.
To make it easier for you to understand, I will show you this video.
I have used the G-texture transfer to create the mesh texture of the plan.
Even if the inner part of the mouth or the nostrils is not perfect,
you can edit it appropriately and use it.
You can output up to 8K,
and with the extra plate function, you can fill in the empty space outside the UV.
Using the z-texture transfer, you can make the mesh texture of the plan into a face mesh,
and then use the z-texture transfer to make the face texture.
Even if the inner part of the mouth or nostrils is not perfect,
you can edit it appropriately.
You can output up to 8K,
and with the extra plate function,
you can fill in the empty space outside the UV.
These are the three factors that I have created.
Among them, the displacement map,
the B-channel,
the micro map,
and the detail normal map have been converted and used.
These are the three physical patterns of the empty space.
The macro map,
the displacement map,
and the detail normal map have been converted and used.
After using the z-brush displacement map,
you can show the details of the skin,
the R-channel,
and the G-channel,
and then adjust the intensity of the O2.
In addition,
the mouth and eye area have been added.
This is the final image of the head model.
If you apply the albedo map,
it looks like this.
Make-up is needed.
That is how it looks like after applying
the albedo map,
this girl looks like she needs to
do skin care and makeup.
After
As a man, I have entered a new field of makeup.
I have seen eye shadow, eye line, and reference.
I have seen pure straight eyebrows and eye line.
I use a lot of eye shadows such as orange, grapefruit, and pink.
I don't know the color of my lips.
I don't know what color is pretty.
I have collected many eye shadow colors and reference pictures of eye lines.
Many people use pure straight eyebrows or slightly drooping eye lines,
and I have collected many eye shadows such as orange, grapefruit, and pink.
I think the color of my lips is similar to the color of my lips.
The most difficult thing for me is that I can't tell what kind of lip color is good.
In order to brighten my skin tone,
I applied a layer mask to the utility map channel in Photoshop to adjust the color.
I applied eye shadow, eye line, cheek touch, eyebrow line, lip tint, blemish remover, and dot makeup.
To make your skin darker,
I used the utility map channel's blood-red and black color pictures to apply them to the layers of the skin.
Then, I adjusted the color.
In the end, I did eye shadow, eye line, blush, hair line, eyebrows, lipstick, and remove the flaws.
That's how the face texture is completed.
This is a comparison of the effect before and after makeup.
Before I made the costume, I made the body first.
I collected the references and compared the proportion and volume.
Now, I'm going to start making the costume.
Before I make the costume, I need to make the body first.
In order to make the body, I collected a lot of reference pictures to see the proportion and shape of the body.
With the history of making body, I began incorporating R substantial and R
representative and R subordinate and Rρούant and added some curve effects.
Now come to make the costume reference.
First of all, make the costume reference.
I have a white t-shirt, a blue jacket, and a black skirt.
The main colors are white and black.
The blue jacket is the top.
Other colors are white, black, and gold.
And this red one is black.
I bought this jacket in the MD store, and I usually buy the clothes in the MD store or download the costume paper to customize it.
I changed the size of the body to fit the body shape, and I combined the small patterns with the small patterns to make it easier to work with the hyper-remote detail.
I made a pose using the Transpose Master in the studio, and I combined the soft with one, and I made a layer, masked the joints, and quickly made a pose with a move or a rotate.
This is the final pose image.
I used the T-Pose Mesh and the Pose Mesh.
I used the Zbrush for the export and the Max for the import.
I used the Wolf animation for the export, and I used the Olympic file for the export.
I included the T-Pose Mesh and the Pose Mesh in the 3D Max to apply the morph, and after applying the animation, I made the Olympic object.
In the Marvelous Designer animation mode, the pre-prepared Alambic file will be inserted, and the clothes will get the same animation effect as the pose.
For the hyper-reliven sculpting work, we plan to rematch the costume mesh with the pose mesh and the unfolded pattern mesh, and export them to OBJ.
The pattern mesh will not be welded, and will be exported in centimeters without thickness.
We imported two OBJ files to 3D Max, and applied morph to them.
To make it easier to understand, the morph is applied to the pattern.
We added two OBJ files to 3D Max, and applied morph to them.
Thank you.
To help you understand better, let's watch the video.
We imported the unfolded pattern mesh from Marvelous Designer, and applied morph to it.
The most famous option is to keep crisp.
This way, the legs will not be broken and will be pretty.
From Marvelous Designer,
we imported the flat-sheet grid from Marvelous Designer to ZBrush.
After rematching, we can unfold it.
The most important option is to keep crisp.
After choosing this option, the edges will not be broken.
We applied the 3D Max morph to the customized costume base mesh, and applied skin wrap to complete the base mesh.
The pattern element is the same.
We added creases and edges on the edges.
When the sub-divide is increased, the pattern can be unfolded.
We added thickness and detailed modeling.
We applied the 3D Max morph to the customized costume base mesh.
This is the final base mesh.
We added creases and details to the edges.
The part of the design is for stacking green.
The 3D mesh was also edited.
We came up with 3D mesh acquisition based on white balcone and white blanny white mesh.
We Disney 3D mesh was made from the hadn then to most of the PruD,
and we drew borders at 3D mesh.
3D mesh is distributed deputy of 3D mesh and many models with 3D mesh.
Then it can display 3D mesh was a forgotten movement.
We created multiple pieces of housing waste as the 3D mesh felt part.
I made only one.
Well, by the way you see.
There is more here.
Yes.
So, I use ZBrush Remesh function.
Although there is a Remesh function in Marvelous Designer, as shown in the picture, the edge of the panel is a triangular grid, and it is a little inconvenient for basemesh after increasing the grid, so I usually use ZBrush Remesh function.
Then I will unwrap in Resume UV and prepare for modeling.
In order to model the posture in detail, I have collected reference images.
I have also referred to the 3D scan image.
It is to refer to the smooth wrinkles and suture lines.
In ZBrush, I increased the sub-divide level, so that the suture line that overlaps with the pattern and the wrinkles that are not expressed in Marvelous are added.
I also made the outer line of the straight line with a harder texture to feel the texture of the denim.
And I made a suture line with a stitch brush.
Then I applied the wrinkle displacement map.
I eased the sub-divide, and the panel became smaller.
For the slot between the panel and the profile of Marvelous Designer, the fold is very difficult, so I repurpose with this fine fold.
In addition, in order to make the tension of the fabric very hard, I added some fold on the fabric.
I use a stitch brush.
The wrinkle texture used in the wrinkle sculpting is also the texture I bought in Texturing XYZ.
I put the texture I bought in Photoshop and edited it according to the UV.
This is the final effect of the model of a cowboy jacket.
Thank you.
I baked and textured in Substance Painter.
I paid attention to the texture of the denim and the pretty washing.
I changed the color of the denim jacket, the washing, and the stitching to see if it matched the character.
The red, orange-colored denim jacket is the second color of Trendra.
I tried and changed the color of the denim jacket, the washing, and the stitching.
I tried to find the best match for my expectation.
Because of the recent trend of loose and bright color, I finally chose the second method.
I wanted to create a kind of Suwan on the gacha side.
I used embroidery and accessories for the gacha side.
I collected reference images and found the right size and position.
I used the
This is my son, X-man.
This is my son, Jisun. He did topology on 3D coat and also baked and textured on Substance Painter.
I also named my son on the button.
I chose hair clip as the highlight of each character.
Before I make the hair cut mesh, I will put the reference hair mesh into ZBrush and make it simple by using DynaMesh.
I will use Ornatrix to make the hair cut mesh.
After setup ZBrush's hair guide mesh, Let me process.
You can easily get the BrockCast2anna
with Ornatrix Hair Guide Mesh.
Ornatrix Hair Guide Mesh.
It is convenient because the Unwrap is automatically organized into a square.
Let's watch the video to help you understand.
After the hair guide mesh made in Zbrush is transparent, the cut mesh is made according to the shape.
Unwrap is a method of processing the hair guide and then turning it into a cut mesh.
The length, width, and rotation of the hair cut mesh can be adjusted on the stack.
Unwrap is also very convenient because it is automatically organized according to the square.
Let's watch the video to help you understand.
Next, let's watch the hair guide mesh made in Zbrush.
Unwrap is a method of processing the hair guide and then turning it into a cut mesh.
After the hair guide mesh isera is completed, it is a hair guide mesh.
This is the final finished hair guide mesh.
Hair texture is made by ZBrush Fiber Mesh.
After creating a variety of Fiber Mesh, it was processed, and the texture was extracted with BPR render.
As you can see, you can extract alpha mask, normal mask, albedo mask, death mask, etc.
This is the ZBrush Fiber Mesh.
As you can see, you can extract alpha mask, normal mask, albedo mask, etc.
This is a video of hair texture arrangement, as you can see, the layer is divided in the card mesh, from the inner layer to the outer layer, making the hair bus more and more messy.
This is a video of hair texture in Mammoth set tool bag.
The disadvantage of card mesh is that it complements the three-dimensional effect.
The left side is hair without hair, and the right side is hair with hair.
I focused on the hair for a more realistic look.
In order to make the eyebrows, I gathered some references to reference the direction of the texture of the eyebrows.
I checked the shape of the eyebrows first.
Then, I checked the shape of Bonatris.
I made the card mesh in the same way as the hair.
I focused on the direction of the eyebrows by referring to the reference image.
I also made the eyebrows texture with the Zimrush Fiber Mesh.
I made the eyebrows texture with the Zimrush Fiber Mesh.
I made several beautiful shapes, for example, one-by-one, one-by-one, one-by-one, and one-by-one.
I made several beautiful shapes, for example, one-by-one, one-by-one, and one-by-one, and one-by-one, and one-by-one, and one-by-one, and one-by-one, and one-by-one.
These are some reference pictures of lighting.
Overall, they are more classic, with a sense of drama.
In order to find the feeling I want,
I made several combinations of lighting and background colors,
but I realized that these were not in line with my ideas,
so I gave up some of them.
So I changed the direction of the design.
I changed the color tone to a bright feeling.
Most of the pictures I found now are some promotional pictures on the commercial website.
I decided to use TAMOS color for the background.
I made lighting and final redding in the marble tool bag.
As you can see, I installed key light, rim light, and fill light,
and chose three-point lighting.
I set up the lighting and final redding in the two bags.
I set up the lighting for key light, rim light, and fill light.
The lighting is set up as an environmental light,
ambient occlusion, key light,
rim light for silhouettes,
I used fill light and GI to express the good choreography.
The rim light is mainly responsible for the image of AO and K-Light.
The fill light is responsible for the dark part of the lighting.
GI is used to express the good choreography.
The rim light is mainly responsible for the image of AO and K-Light.
This is the final finished image.
Our radio station is the address and our youtube channel address
through which you can get information anytime.
This is a personal